Guide to the National Lesbian and Gay Health Association records, 1978-1992.
National Lesbian and Gay Health Association records,
- Series II. Conference Files
  - Technical assistance files, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Workshop session planning materials, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Youth institute, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Regional conference, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Advertising, Conference 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits, Conference 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Photos for conference program, Conference 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Press, Conference 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photos for conference program (?), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - News clippings, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Meeting notes, correspondence, Conference 1991? (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Photo negatives ffrom conferences (?), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Conference Session Cassette Recordings
    - Outreach- Services, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 3: Internalized Homophobia/Gay & Lesbian, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 4: Support Groups/Blacks AIDS, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 5: Hospital Response- AIDS Crisis, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 6: AIDS 101, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 7: Make Room for Healing & Dying, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 9: Counseling & Socialization as Therapeutic, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape13: History of PWA Movement, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 14: Defining Anti-gay Violence, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 15: Effective Lobbying, Private, Federal, Local, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 16: Looking Past Addictive Behavior, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 19: Sexual Preference to Physicians, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 67: Homophobia, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Black Persons Laughing at AIDS, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Lesbian Parenting, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Compulsive Sexual Behavior, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - AIDS Risk Reduction- outreach, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Neurological Issues, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Loss of Sexual Powers, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Being Wonderfully Well, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Corporate & Business Funding (2 tapes), Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Sexual Exploitating Politically, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - AIDS Prevention for Youth, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 24: AIDS Education for Children & Youth, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Developing Local Resources, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 27: Working with Soropositive Individuals, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 28: Hemophilia & AIDS, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 29: Analysis of Insurance, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 33: Lesbian Health Survey, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 33B: Lesbian Health, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 37: HV Antibody, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 38: Homecare AIDS/ARC, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Commerce/Education, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 42: National Review, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Unlabeled, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 47: Shame Based Family Systems, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 51: Turning a Corner- Political, Civil (2 tapes), Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 53: Government Healthcare, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 54: Plenary, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tape 63: Issues AZT, Conference 1987 (Box 13)
- Series III. FARO
  - Founding minutes, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Steering committee list, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wipe-Out-AIDS! funding proposal, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - AIDS forum, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - FARO projects, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Regional representation plan, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Steering committee meetings and agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Steering committee/coordinating committee/members memos, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - FARO Update, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Lobby Project reports, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Membership, steering committee, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Minutes of FARO meeting (verbatim), draft copt, Aug. 1983 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Resource Directory draft, Nov. 1983 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Directory of AIDS Resources materials, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Steering committee meeting edited minutes, Nov. 1983 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Press releases, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Press coverage, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Resource Clearing House (RCH) reports/descriptions, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - RCH funding plans, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - AIDS Forum (3rd annual) report/memo, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Denver AIDS forum report, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - FARO introductory materials, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Steering committee annual meeting, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Steering committee meeting edited minutes, Feb. 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Annual meeting, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Meeting agenda, June 1984 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence/reports, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Cost sharing, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Dues receipts, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous reports, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - FARO Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - "New" (correspondence from W. Batchelor, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - RCH Director job description, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - FARO Update originals, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - RCH Budget, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Series IV. Publicity/Publications
  - NLGHF brochures, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - NGHEF brochure, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Newsletter plans, 1984, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - NGHEF newsletter, Lesbian & Gay Health, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - NLGHF CheckUp, Spring 1990 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Press coverage of the NGHEF, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Press releases, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Lesbian Health Care Survey press release, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Sourcebook press releases, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Press releases, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
  - NGLHF publications, 1983-1984, 1988, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Publications orders, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - National Lesbian/Gay Health Directory listing request, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Directory orders, paid, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Directory: 2nd edition materials, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Directory: 3rd edition materials, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Directory: 4th edition materials, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Directory orders/Sourcebook orders, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Sourcebook materials, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Sourcebook on Lesbian/Gay Health Care, 1st edition (unbound), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sourcebook on Lesbian/Gay Health Care, 1st edition (bound), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sourcebook materials, NGHC and caucuses, 1984? (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sourcebook correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sourcebook materials, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Sourcebook press research, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Sourcebook requests/correspondence, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
  - Sourcebook materials: Shernoff, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Sourcebook listing, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Sourcebook orders, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Sourcebook brochure, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Sourcebook materials, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
  - Sexual Health Reports, printed by the NLGHF, v.9 no.2, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence requests for publications, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Travel arrangements, Conference 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lesbian & Gay Health publication title mock-up, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Series V. Subject Files
  - Topical
    - ACME (Alliance for Continuing Medical Education) Conference program, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - AIDS and healthcare providers: guidlines and precautions, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - AIDS brochures, non-governmental reports and statements, 1984-1985? (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - AIDS: European response, 1983? (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - AIDS: Federal/state/local reports and studies, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - AIDS: The Immune System, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - AIDS: Media (electronic) responses, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - AIDS miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - AIDS miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - AIDS: Non-governmental, professional reports/updates/articles, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - AIDS packet of information, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Alcohol and drug abuse, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Australia- National AIDS Bulletin, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Black and Hispanic inclusion, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Committee for Public Health Awareness, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Death and dying (pamphlets), 1978, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Gay Nurses' Alliance press release/correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Gay Student Services v. Texan A & M: Amicus APHA, 1982? (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Health and disability rights, 1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Hepatitis B, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Hospice and home care for PWAs, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Howard Brown Memorial Clinic, Chicago, IL, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - HRC direct mail, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - HTLV-III antibody test, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - International Lesbian & Gay Association Conference papers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Lesbian and gay healthcare emergence, 1980-1984 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Los Angeles G/L Community Center, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Mayor Koch (NY) statement on AIDS, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - National Lesbian Health Care Survey Mental Health Implications, labeled "For Administrative Use Only", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - National Lesbian Health Care Survey mental Health Implications, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - National Lesbian Health Care Survey Final Report, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Resources, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Moral Majority/Jerry Falwell direct mail, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Mother and Child Health in Africa conference brochure, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - New York: delegates and contacts, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - "Reports on AIDS" published in the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, June 1981-Jan.1985 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Sexual compulsion, 1985? (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Sexually Transmitted Disease Screening, Casefinding, and Education Agreement, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Paper entitled "Some Correlates of Racism, Sexism, and Homophobia Among Undergraduate Social Work Students", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - STDs, 1982, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Toxoplasmosis, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Women and AIDS/Women' healthcare, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - The Washington Blade, Oct. 16, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Organizations
    - AID Atlanta, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action Council, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Project/Los Angeles, 1982, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ammerican Association of Physicians for Human Rights (AAPHR), 1982, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Floriday state-wide AIDS organizations, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - National Gay Task Force (NGTF), 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia AIDS Task Force, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Shanti Project, 1975, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Alaska Home Healthcare (Anchorage), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Arizona, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - CA: AIDS Health Project publications FOCUS,UCSF, San Francisco, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - CA: AIDS Project Los Angeles, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - CA: University of California San Francisco AIDSline, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - CA: ARIS Project, Santa Clara County, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - CA: Beverly Foundations, Pasadena, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - CA: AIDS Response Program, Orange County n.d. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - CA: California AIDS Update, by State Senator David Roberti, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - CA: Documentation of AIDS Issues and Research Foundation (DAIR) Update (publication), 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - CA: 18th St. Services brochure, San Francisco, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - CA: Eroticus, San Francisco- Hot & Healthy Times, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - CA: Exodus Trust, San Francisco, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - CA: Healing AIDS publication, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - CA: Institute for Advanced Study of Human Sexuality, San Francisco, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Lazarus Project seminar cassette tapes lists, 1986? (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - The Network (Computerized AIDS Information Network), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - CA: San Francisco AIDS Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - CA: San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS conference program, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - CA: Shanti Project, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - CA: Southern CA Women for Understanding, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - CA: The Wishing Well publication, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - CA: People With AIDS/ARC switchboard, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - CA: People With AIDS Update, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - CA: The United States Mission, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - CA: Women and AIDS, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - CA: Womancare clinic, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - CO: Colorado AIDS Project Update, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - CT: The Philanthropy Monthly, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - FL organizations, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - FL: Center One, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - FL: Escambia AIDS Services & Education, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - FL: Florida Keys Memorial Hospital, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - FL: Florida Association of Pediatric Tumor Programs, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - FL: Monroe County Health Unit AIDS Education Project, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - GA: AID Atlanta, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - HI: The Life Foundation, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Illinois, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - IL: Chicago Resource Center, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - IL: Midwest Women's Center, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - IL: The Sophia Fund, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - IN: Indiana AIDS Task Force, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - IN: Justice, Inc., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - LA: NO/AIDS Task Force, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - ME: AIDS Project News, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - MD: American College Health Association, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - MD: Feeling Great Diamond Publication, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - MD: HERO, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - MD: Maryland Cares, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - MD: Johns Hopkins University, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - MA: AIDS Action Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - MA: Massachusetts Gay & Lesbian Political Caucus, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - MA: Greater Boston Lesbian & Gay Political Alliance, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - MA: Provincetown AIDS Support Group, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - MA: Provincetown Positive PWA Coalition, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - MI: Wellness Networks Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - MN: PWA live, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - MN: Metropolitan Community Mental Health Center, 1984? (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - MN: Minnesota Center for Grief and Loss, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - MN: PMS Clinic of Minneapolis, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - MN: Pride Institute, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - MO: The Pink Triangle Report, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - MO: Good Samaritan Project, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - NJ: Self-Help Clearinghouse, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - NJ: Seabrook House (recovery), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - NY: AIDS Task Force of Central NY, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - NY: Brooklyn AIDS Task Force, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - NY: Community Health Project, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - NY: CUNY Lesbian & Gay Community News, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - NY: GMHC Treatment Issues, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - NY: Gay Officers Action League (GOAL), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - NY: God's Love We Deliver, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - NY: Interfaith Medical Center, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - NY: Lesbian & Gay Community Service Center, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - NY: Lesbian Interest Press, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - NY: Men of All Colors Together, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - NY: Multitasking Systems/New York, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - NY: NYC Comptroller L/G Services/Resource Directory, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - NY: NYC Department of Health AIDS Education Unit, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - NY: NY State Department of Health "100 Q+A on AIDS", 1986 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - NY: The Pilgrim, newsletter of the Lazzaro Center, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - NY: PWA Coalition, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - NY: SIECUS NYU, 1986-1989 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - SAGE, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - NY: Spellman Center for Treatment of PWAs, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - NY: St. Clare's Hospital Dental Clinic (PWA/ARC), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - NY: St. Mark's Women' Health Collective, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - NY: Wise Woman Center, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - NC: Forsyth County Health Department, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - NC: Lesbian and Gay Health Project of North Carolina, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - NC: Triad Health Project, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - OH: Columbus AIDS Task Force, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - OH: Good Times publication, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - PA: Lazarus Ministry (MCC), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - PA: Philadelphia AIDS Task Force, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - PA: We The People publication, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - PA: Working Group on Lesbian Battering, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - TX: Austin AIDS Project, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - TX: Lifeline publication of the AIDS Foundation Houston, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - TX: PWA Coalition of Dallas, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - VA: Fan Free Clinic, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - VA: Health Alert- Creative Media Group, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - VA: Opportunities Unlimited, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - VA: Virginia Commonwealth University Gay and Lesbian Student Alliance pamphlet, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - WA, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - WV: Gay and Lesbian Alliance of West Virginia University, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - WV: WV Department of Health AIDS Prevention/Education, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - WI: Among Friends, 1987, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - WI: Madison AIDS Support Network, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Washington, DC: DC Governemtn AIDS Efforts, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - DC: Department of Human Services, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - DC: DC Office of Human Rights, 1986, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - DC: Dupont West Medical Center, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - DC: MCC Disciples, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - DC: National Latino Lesbian/Gay Activists, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - DC: Sexual Minority Youth Assistance League (SMYAL), 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - DC: Washington Area Council on Alcoholism & Drug Abuse (WACADA), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - DC: Whitman-Walker Clinic, 1985-1986. (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Series VI. Miscellany
  - 6 cassette tapes (labeled 1-6): NIMH minority AIDS meeting, June 10, 1986 (Box 13)
  - 2 unlabeled cassette tapes, note states "This set recorded direct from video", n.d. (Box 13)
  - Anti-AIDS teddy bear pin (Box 13)
  - Stamp: "Pay To The Order of The Amalgamated Bank of New York NGHEF/FARO" (Box 13)
  - Stamp: "For Deposit Only Paul Paroski, JR. Scholarship Fund (Box 13)
  - Stamp: "Pay To The Order of The Amalgamated Bank of New York National Gay Health Education Foundation" (Box 13)
  - VHS Tape: "America Responds to AIDS", Spring 1989, V-366
  - VHS Tape: "AIDS: Questions And Answers", 1986, V-367
  - VHS Tape: "Needle Talk", by the NYC Department of Health, 1987, V-368